

MAREK KOBYLARCZYK

Junior Front-end Developer

ABOUT ME

My name is Marek Kobylarczyk and I'm junior Front-end Developer. I finished high school with a certificate of IT Specialist. I learn new technologies on my own from many websites. Web development is something I've always wanted to do.

ADDRESS

Szpitalna 12/15, Marki, Poland

ENGLISH

B1

PHONE

+48 732 013 413

marek.kobylarczyk@gmail.com

https://github.com/marek9499

WEBSITE

https://marek9499.github.io/portfolio



HOBBIES



SOFT SKILLS

- PHOTOGRAPHY
- IOT
- BIKE TOURS
- COOKING
- FASHION
- TEAM PLAYER
- COMMUNICATIVE
- FAST LEARNER
- OPEN-MINDED



EXPERIENCE

Customer Advisor, Samsung Brand Store, Warsaw September 2019 - September 2020

- Customer service in the field of sales (also technical)
- Implementation of entrusted sales plans
- Cooperation with the sales / marketing department
- · Taking care of Visual Merchandising
- · Acting as a Samsung Brand Ambassador

Junior Sales Advisor, Samsung Electronics, Warsaw March 2018 - March 2019

- Presentation of available Samsung products and services
- · Active sale of devices and services
- Installing software on devices
- Taking care of product exposure
- Performing the role of Samsung representative



EDUCATION

IT Specialist, Zespół Szkół Elektronicznych im. Bohaterów Westerplatte, Radom

September 2013 - April 2017



SKILLS

Advanced knowledge of:

- HTML5
- CSS3 (BEM)
- SCSS
- Mobile First
- Javascript (ES5+)
- ExpressJS
- MongoDB
- REST API

Basic knowledge of:

- React
- ¡Query
- NodeJS
- UX/UI
- Handlebars Figma
- PHP MySQL
- Adobe XD
- SOL
- Wordpress
- GIT
- Bootstrap



PROJECTS

WeatherApp

github

My first, more extensive project based on frontend and backend, where the user can check the weather for the upcoming hours for many cities.

TodoApp

github

SPA project written as part of learning the javascript language. The logic of the script is to add / remove tasks in a very simple graphic design.

Rzeczoznawca majątkowy

github

That was the first commercial project that I had to implement in a very short period time. However, full responsiveness has been maintained.

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal DataProtection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the EuropeanParliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on thefree movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".